But another, more salient realization that comes to light is the triviality of our own self-importance and self-consciousness. To truly understand the extent to which your self-consciousness prohibits you from engaging in opportunities should lead everyone to take risks they otherwise wouldn't. We're merely a blip on the time line of the universe, right? Act accordingly. Now the ideas that I'm presenting today were imbued upon me through some otherwise unfortunate circumstances, granted, but they're lying dormant in the lives of anyone who's willing to exploit them. If we all understand that we all have unique weaknesses, and if we're honest about what they are, we can learn how to best take advantage of them, whether they be mounting a curb or fear of presenting sales reports or the inability to sufficiently manage one's finances -- looking at that guy -- (Laughter) there lies the ability to learn, to adapt, and even the ability to rewire one's instinctual response to challenges. Adversity is good, and it has the potential to make you stronger. And, at the very least, you can scare the hell out of kids if you look like a pirate. Thanks. (Applause and cheers)
Otra revelación más importante que sale a la luz es lo trivial de las propias arrogancia y vergüenza. Comprender hasta qué punto tu sentido del ridículo te impide aprovechar las oportunidades debería permitir a la gente tomar riesgos que no tomarían. Solo somos un instante en la línea temporal del universo. Actúen como tal. Las ideas que hoy les presento me fueron infundidas por alguna que otra circunstancia desafortunada, pero están latentes en la vida de quien quiera aprovecharse de ellas. Si entendemos que todos tenemos debilidades y somos honestos sobre estas aprenderemos cómo sacarles partido al máximo. Ya sea subir a una acera, presentar un informe de ventas o la incapacidad de gestionar nuestro dinero de forma eficiente, estoy mirando a ese tipo ... (Risas) Permanece la capacidad de aprender, de adaptarse e incluso la de cambiar la respuesta a las dificultades. La adversidad es positiva y tiene el potencial de hacerte más fuerte. Y, en última instancia, puedes espantar a los niños si pareces un pirata. Gracias. (Aplausos y vítores)